Guide to the Fred W. Voget Papers 1935-1996
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photos, 1939-1989; Series VI; 2.5 linear feet
  - Kitchen crew in buffalo pasture, circa 1973 (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):539)
  - People by tents, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):540)
  - Vehicles in deep shadow, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):541)
  - Marshall, Melvin, Frederick, and Anthony Left Hand standing by truck with Everett Whiteman, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):542)
  - View of houses from hill, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):543)
  - View of houses from hill, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):544)
  - Distant view of man herding small number of cattle, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):545)
  - Black Canyon Youth Camp, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):546)
  - Black Canyon Youth Camp, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):547)
  - Black Canyon Youth Camp, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):548)
  - Peter Plenty Hawk standing by truck, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):549)
  - Clothesline with unidentified objects in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):550)
  - Partially constructed sun dance lodge, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):551)
  - Tarp/covered pile in fenced enclosure, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):552)
  - Lodge Grass High School, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):553)
  - Older man and woman, both with braids, in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):554)
  - Older man and woman, both with braids, in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):555)
  - Older man with braids, seated, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):556)
  - Overexposed photo of man and woman in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):557)
  - Two men seated on bench, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):558)
  - Woman typing, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):559)
  - Woman typing, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):560)
  - Blackfeet tribal office, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):561)
  - Blackfeet tribal office, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):562)
  - Cabin with trees in background, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):563)
  - Distant view of house, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):564)
  - View of building, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):565)
  - View of downtown street, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):566)
  - View of dirt road with houses, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):567)
  - View of building, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):568)
  - View of street, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):569)
  - Man standing in front of doorway, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):570)
  - Man and woman in front of tent and car, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):571)
  - Three small children in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):572)
  - Man on tractor, undated (Box-folder 26/61, Photo number 318(VI):573)
  - Man and woman on dirt path, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):574)
  - Man on dirt path, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):575)
  - Woman on dirt path, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):576)
  - View of small houses, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):577)
  - Man standing near stone monument, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):578)
  - Station wagon in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):579)
  - Small house, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):580)
  - View of distant houses, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):581)
  - View of distant houses, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):582)
  - View of building with some snow, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):583)
  - Woman leaving downtown building, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):584)
  - Four children in front of houses, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):585)
  - View of downtown street, undated (Box-folder 26/62, Photo number 318(VI):586)
  - Man in front of museum-type wall display, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):587)
  - Man in front of museum-type wall display, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):588)
  - Seated man taking notes, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):589)
  - Seated man taking notes, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):590)
  - Man at record player, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):591)
  - Man at record player, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):592)
  - Logs in front of shed, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):593)
  - Logs by shed, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):594)
  - Man on tractor, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):595)
  - Man on tractor, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):596)
  - Boys seated by pulley or winch, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):597)
  - Pile of scrap lumber, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):598)
  - Man posed by building, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):599)
  - View of cabin at Pryor, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):600)
  - William Big Day and his wife by house by house in Pryor, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):601)
  - Teepee frame at Pryor, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):602)
  - Man in front of stone monument, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):603)
  - Cattle in pasture, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):604)
  - Little Big Horn Battlefield, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):605)
  - Little Big Horn Battlefield, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/63, Photo number 318(VI):606)
  - Three children, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):607)
  - Bends family, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):608)
  - Man with three children, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):609)
  - Adlow Harris and children, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):610)
  - Joe Medicine Crow, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):611)
  - John Whiteman and Amy with the Fritterer brothers in front of house, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):612)
  - Small boy, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):613)
  - Three children, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):614)
  - Man seated on sofa, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):615)
  - Priest standing by small boy, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):616)
  - Adlow Harris with baby and two children, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):617)
  - Woman on swing set, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):618)
  - Seated man, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):619)
  - Five unidentified adults, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):620)
  - Man and woman in traditional Native American attire, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):621)
  - Children in truck, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):622)
  - House and shed, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):623)
  - Row of houses, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):624)
  - Church, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):625)
  - Building, undated (Box-folder 26/64, Photo number 318(VI):626)
  - Residential street, undated (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):627)
  - Trees, undated (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):628)
  - Parade float, circa 1950s (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):629)
  - House and barn in the distance, undated (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):630)
  - Houses in the distance, undated (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):631)
  - Houses, undated (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):632)
  - Joe Blaine, Matthew Good Luck, Steve Bird, Herbert Blanc, and Josephine Gets Down drumming, undated (Box-folder 26/65, Photo number 318(VI):633)
  - Man with child in stroller, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):634)
  - Man holding child, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):635)
  - Boy and toddler, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):636)
  - Man and boy, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):637)
  - Four children, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):638)
  - Five children, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):639)
  - Two men in shadow, seated in front of blackboard, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):640)
  - Audience in shadow, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):641)
  - Three people seated at desk, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):642)
  - Three people seated at desk, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):643)
  - Audience, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):644)
  - House, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):645)
  - House, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):646)
  - Men standing outside of building, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):647)
  - Large white house, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):648)
  - Small yellow house, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):649)
  - Arrow throw competition, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):650)
  - Arrow throw competition, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):651)
  - Five adults posed in front of store, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):652)
  - Two people on horseback visiting with two other people, undated (Box-folder 26/66, Photo number 318(VI):653)
  - Clara Bends, Agnes Yellowtail, Feral Ease, Bill Ease, and three children posed in front of Crow Indian Baptist Mission, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):654)
  - White house with fence, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):655)
  - Two people on horseback visiting with woman and two children, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):656)
  - Boy, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):657)
  - Log house, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):658)
  - Two women seated on bench, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):659)
  - Distant view of truck, corrals, and shed, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):670)
  - Two men on horseback and three cars, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):671)
  - Castle Rocks, Pryor, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):672)
  - Castle Rocks, Pryor, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):673)
  - Man by loaded truck, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):674)
  - Tarp covered mound, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):675)
  - Crow Agency BIA, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):676)
  - People seated in shadow, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):677)
  - Teepee and tent, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):678)
  - Man on porch in shadow, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):679)
  - Man in front of small house, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):680)
  - Man in front of porch, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):681)
  - Man in field by gray house, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):682)
  - Man in field by gray house, undated (Box-folder 26/67, Photo number 318(VI):683)
  - Crow sun dance preparatory dance, Tom Yellowtail, medicine man, and Thomas Lion Shows, sponsor, 1975 (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):684)
  - Praying and singing over center pole before raising, 1975 (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):685)
  - Veteran Joe Blaine marking pole with charcoal, 1975 (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):686)
  - Dancer in traditional Crow sun dance attire, undated (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):687)
  - Marshall and Ira Lefthand, circa 1976 (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):688)
  - Three Crow boys on horses, 1975 (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):689)
  - Six Nations band, undated (Box-folder 26/68, Photo number 318(VI):690)
  - Spear Siding above Lodge Grass, Montana, undated (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):691)
  - Poles for dance stalls, Crow sun dance, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):692)
  - People gathered inside sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):693)
  - Man in street clothes seated in lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):694)
  - Overexposed view inside sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):695)
  - Joe Alden, Retard Carter, and others at sunrise service on last day, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):696)
  - Overexposed view of people inside sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):697)
  - Overexposed view of people inside sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):698)
  - Overexposed view of people inside sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):699)
  - People entering sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):700)
  - Sun dancers getting soup and soda pop after dance, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):701)
  - Sun dancer in front of car, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):702)
  - Man seated in shadow, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):703)
  - People outside sun dance lodge, 1975 (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):704)
  - People standing and seated by car, undated (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):705)
  - People outside of sun dance lodge, undated (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):706)
  - John Truhujo standing in front of tents, undated (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):707)
  - James Bear Below and Gladys Ann Littleness seated under canopy, undated (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):708)
  - People around table by white house, undated (Box-folder 26/69, Photo number 318(VI):709)
  - Janice Old Crow with child in river, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):710)
  - Three children in Little Big Horn River, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):711)
  - Child in Little Big Horn River, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):712)
  - Janice Old Crow rinsing pants in Little Big Horn River, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):713)
  - Frederick Left Hand and three children in Little Big Horn River, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):714)
  - Four children in Little Big Horn River, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):715)
  - One person in Little Big Horn River, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):716)
  - Boy riding bareback, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):717)
  - Truck by portable outhouse, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):718)
  - Boy and horse in front of rickety cabin, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):719)
  - Two men and two horses, one man shoeing horse, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):720)
  - Man shoeing horse, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):721)
  - Crow Fair arena with bucking bull in center, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):722)
  - Crow Fair arena with racing horses coming in on far side, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):723)
  - Crow Fair arena with racing horse coming in on far side, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):724)
  - Crow Fair arena with bucking bull in center, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):725)
  - Sunset shot with Wolf Mountains in very distant background, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):726)
  - Sunset shot with Wolf Mountains in very distant background, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):727)
  - Very distant shot of fire at treetop level, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):728)
  - Very distant shot of fire at treetop level, undated (Box-folder 26/70, Photo number 318(VI):729)
  - Yellow robe, first recipient of Pete Lefthand Award, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):730)
  - Sunset shot by water, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):731)
  - Statue of man and horse in Cody, Wyoming, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):732)
  - Gathering of people in shadows, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):733)
  - Joe Medicine Crow, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):734)
  - Man, woman, and boy in foreground, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):735)
  - Santa Maria, undated (Box-folder 26/71, Photo number 318(VI):736)